{
  "type": "fill_in_the_blank_list",
  "title": "Fill in the List (1 points each blank, 59 total)",
  "instructions": "Type the correct answer(s) in the blank(s).",
  "points_per_question": 1,
  "questions": [
    {
      "prompt": "Name the four types of interface (input) modalities for games ___ ___ ___ ___",
      "answers": [["inertial","touch","audio","video"]]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "What are the fundamental attributes of games according to Chris Crawford? \n___ \n___ \n___ \n___",
      "answers": [["representation","interaction","conflict","safety"]]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "What are Bartle's Player Types? \n___ \n___ \n___ \n___",
      "answers": [["killers","achievers","explorers","socializers","killer","achiever","explorer","socializer"]]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "List Quantic Foundry's Gamer Types: ___ ___ ___ ___ ___ ___ ___ ___ ___",
      "answers": [["acrobat","gardener","slayer","skirmisher","gladiator","ninja","bounty hunter","architect","bard"]]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "List Quantic Foundry's Motivation Clusters: ___ ___ ___ ___ ___ ___",
      "answers": [["action","mastery","social","creativity","immersion","achievement"]]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "List Quantic Foundry's Gamer Motivations: ___ ___ ___ ___ ___ ___ ___ ___ ___ ___ ___ ___",
      "answers": [["destruction","excitement","competition","community","challenge","strategy","completion","power","fantasy","story","design","discovery"]]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "What are the three parts of the MDA framework? \n___ \n___ \n___",
      "answers": [["mechanics","dynamics","aesthetics", "mechanic","dynamic","aesthetic"]]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "List six major genres of video games (super-genres, not sub-genres): ___ ___ ___ ___ ___ ___",
      "answers": [["action","adventure","role-playing", "rpg", "simulation","sim","sports","sport","strategy","puzzle","idle","racing","race", "fighting", "horror", "educational", "social deduction", "visual novel"]]
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Name four of the eight types of fun: ___ ___ ___ ___",
      "answers": [["sensation","fantasy","narrative","challenge","fellowship","discovery","expression","submission", "competition"]] 
    },
    {
      "prompt": "Name the major 9th generation consoles: ___ ___ ___",
      "answers": [["playstation 5","xbox series x","xbox series", "xbox series s", "xbox series x/s", "xbox series s/x", "nintendo switch","ps5","xbox","switch","nintendo switch 2","switch 2","switch2", "steamdeck", "steam deck"]]
    }
  ]
}